Hello, welcome to our show.
你好，欢迎来到我们的节目。
Today we have a special guest,
今天我们有一位特别的嘉宾，
John Doe, who is an expert
约翰·多伊，他是一位专家
in the field of artificial intelligence.
人工智能领域的专家。
John, can you tell us
约翰，你能告诉我们
a bit about your background?
一些关于你背景的信息吗？
Sure, I'd be happy to.
当然，我很乐意。
I started my career
我开始我的职业生涯
as a software engineer
作为一名软件工程师
and then transitioned into AI.
然后转向人工智能领域。
It's been an incredible journey.
这是一段不可思议的旅程。
What inspired you to get into AI?
是什么激发了你进入人工智能领域的兴趣？
I've always been fascinated
我一直对机器的潜力感到着迷，
by the potential of machines
它们能够学习并模仿人类智能。
to learn and mimic human intelligence.
That's what drove me to explore this field.
这就是促使我探索这个领域的原因。
What are some of the challenges
有哪些挑战
you face in your work?
是你在工作中面临的？
One of the biggest challenges.
最大的挑战之一。
is the ethical implications
是伦理问题
of AI development.
在人工智能的发展中。
We need to ensure that
我们需要确保人工智能被负责任地使用，
AI is used responsibly
并且不侵犯人权。
and does not infringe on human rights.
Thank you for sharing your insights.
谢谢你分享你的见解。
You're welcome. It's been a pleasure.
不客气。这是我的荣幸。